psychologicalscience.org 2010-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Association for Psychological Science

The Association for Psychological Science values the privacy of its Members and other visitors to this web site. This document details how we gather and disseminate user information. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy.

**Use of Internet Protocol Address**  
We use your Internet protocol (IP) address for several reasons: to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our web site, and to gather broad demographic information.

**Use of Membership Information**  
The Association for Psychological Science only uses the information collected on the APS web site for the specified purpose.

When you submit a membership application, the Association for Psychological Science requests information such as contact (i.e. name and e-mail address), demographic (i.e. ZIP code and gender), and order information. The contact information you provide is used to send orders and APS information. On occasion, we rent member’s mailing addresses to third-party companies, however we do not divulge any other information (i.e. a user’s e-mail address, telephone number, or birth date) to outside companies.

You may request that your name and address not be provided to third parties by writing:

**Association for Psychological Science**  
1133 15th Street, NW  
Suite 1000  
Washington, DC 20005  
USA

Telephone: +1 202.293.9300, Fax: +1 202.293.9350

Your financial information is used for the sole purpose of billing you for products and services you have ordered. Credit card information is used only for completing the specific transaction for which the credit card information was supplied. APS does not collect or save credit card information.

**Security**  
The Association for Psychological Science features security measures [verified by Verisign](https://seal.verisign.com/splash?form_file=fdf/splash.fdf&dn=WWW.PSYCHOLOGICALSCIENCE.ORG&lang=en "Verisign Secure Site") to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information placed under our control.

This site uses cookies to enhance the visitor’s experience. A cookie is a small text file that our web server places on a user’s computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Cookies enable Association for Psychological Science to track usage patterns. Members can elect to have their password saved to a cookie for logging into the site. Our cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. Note: your browser must be set to allow cookies for this feature to work.

**Children’s Guidelines**  
The Association for Psychological Science is a member-based organization and the services, products, and information are not intended for children.

**Correct/Update Personal Information**  
The Association for Psychological Science allows you to change or modify your personal information by visiting http://www.psychologicalscience.org/members/member_change.cfm.

**Disclaimer**  
This site contains links to other sites. Association for Psychological Science is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any additional questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us:

**Association for Psychological Science**  
1133 15th street, NW, Suite 1000  
Washington, DC 20005  
USA  
Telephone: +1 202.293.9300, Fax: +1 202.293.9350  
Contact APS
